

Tobiasz Porębski

tobiasz.porebski@gmail.com github.com/tobhash +48 725 437 303 linkedin.com/in/tobiasz-porebski

Interested in technology and science. Passionate about teaching and mentoring with over 5 years of experience in conducting programming and robotics classes. Privately a scout, cook and winemaker. Like board & video games, hiking and a good book.

Technical Skills Languages: Python, Java, C#, C, JavaScript, SQL

Software: Git, Jira, Visual Studio, PyCharm, IntelliJ, MS Office,

Concepts: Manual & Automated Testing, Agile methodology, Kanban

Mindset: Fast learning, creative, problem solving, analytical, calm, balanced

Experience

Trainer / Robotowo, Cracow

Sep 2019 - Aug 2021

Organizing training meetings for my team to improve the comprehension of the technologies used. Supporting the growth of an instructors team in the process of preparation and conducting classes. Creating collections of materials and scenarios used during the classes.

Technical Coordinator / Robotowo, Cracow

Sep 2018 - Sep 2019

Maintenance, repairs and testing of classroom equipment and software. Preparation of training materials and procedures. Initiating and implementing optimization activities. Conducting workshops at events organized by ABB and CISCO.

Robotics and Programming Workshop Instructor / Robotowo, Cracow

Sep 2016 - Sep 2018

Conducting robotics and programming classes using Python and C language for Processing, RaspberryPi, ArduinoUno projects and educational LEGO sets: Mindstorms, NXT and WeDo.

Game Programming Instructor / EduExe, Cracow

Sep 2014 - Oct 2015

Conducting game programming classes for children and teenagers in Scratch and Java. Conducting algorithmics classes for high school groups.

Certificates

ISTQB Certified Tester Foundation Level Credential ID 10539/FLCT/2018

IREB Certified Professional for Requirements Engineering Foundation Level Credencial ID 00101/FLIREB/2018

Education

Computer Science / Jagiellonian University

Sep 2014 - Jan 2017

5 semesters out of 6 Bachelor's studies.

Active member of a Computer Science Student's Association of the Jagiellonian University. Workshop conductor, events and concerts announcer.

Electrotechnics / AGH University of Technology and Science

Oct 2012 - Feb 2014

3 semesters out of 7 Bachelor's studies.

Courses

In progress:

Udemy.com: Master Software Testing+Jira+Agile on Live App-Be a TeamLead

Automated Software Testing with Python

edX.com: Cloud Application Development Foundations

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).